

### **CONTACT ME**

09085168569

serafinmarkjay@gmail.com

#125 Don Primitivo St. Brgy. Holy Spirit, Quezon City

#### **CORE SKILLS**

- Computer Literate (Microsoft word, PowerPoint, excel)
- Basic Troubleshooting
- Computer Programming (php, java, JavaScript)
- Basic knowledge about C, C++,
  C# programming language
- Marketing
- Digital Arts
- Brand Digital Marketing

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Good communication skill
- Hardworking, industrious, and eager to learn
- Leadership

#### LANGUAGE

- Tagalog
- English

# SERAFIN,

## MARK JAY P.

To apply for a work in a friendly and humane organization where my skills and knowledge can be utilized to the fullest. A job that will highlight both of my core and soft skills that will not only help the company but my personal growth as well. Hoping that I can learn and enrich my existing knowledge and skills to further specialize my potential work opportunities.

## **EDUCATION**

### Quezon City University, 2019-2023

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (College)

- College of Computer Studies
- Graduated with Latin Honor (Cum Laude)
- GWA: 1.52
- Graduated as Scholar of QCYDO

#### Mary the Queen College of Quezon City, Inc., 2017-2019

Information and Communication Technology (Senior High School)

- Graduated with Honor
- Outstanding Performance in Language (Silver)
- Outstanding Performance in Communication (Gold)
- Outstanding Performance in Social Science (Silver)
- Outstanding Performance in Physical Education and Health (Silver)

#### Judge Feliciano Belmonte Sr. High School, 2013-2017

Junior High School

#### PRIMARY EDUCATION

#### Old Balara Elementary School, 2006-2013

Graduated with Leadership Award

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# ★ Business Development Specialist

# October 2023 - Present MD Channel

- Work as Business Development Specialist
- Finding ways to promote brands
- Communicating with brand regarding approval, requirements, guidelines etc.
- Looking for affiliates to promote the brand we're handling
- Organizing, planning, and attending events as a sponsor for brand/s.
- Market the brands during the said events.

# Customer Experience Agent

June 2022 - January 2023

#### Alorica Teleservices Inc.

- Work as a Customer Experience Agent
- Line of Business is Magenta Telesales
- Handled one of the largest US based Telecommunication account (T-Mobile) as a Sales Representative/Expert
- Provides customer support in placing orders, adding of line/s, and account creation

# 🌟 IT Support (Internship)

September 2022 - March 2023

#### Tech Mahindra LTD.

- Does On the Job Training
- IT Support supervised by IT TIM Engineers Senior
- Provides Troubleshooting/Issues Solving in production floor
- Does reimage, installation of basic applications, machine clean up, machine replacements, updation of McAfee security, and compliance
- Carry out IT Asset and Machine Inventory

# TRAINING ATTENDED/CERTIFICATIONS

# Computer System Servicing NCII

#### October 26, 2018

- Awarded at Mary the Queen College of Quezon City, Inc.
- Installing and configuring computer system
- Preparing lan cables
- Setting up a computer system
- Setting up a server computer
- Connecting and remoting of server and workstation
- · Assembling and Disassembling of machine

# TRAINING ATTENDED/CERTIFICATIONS

## **Fundamentals of Networking**

#### November 09, 2022

- Awarded at Tech Mahindra LTD.
- · Setting up the compliant machine
- Installation of basic applications
- · Setting up lan cables
- · Sharing of files from one machine to another

# SCHOLARSHIP GRANTS

#### Saint Benedict Parish Scholarship Program

#### 2014 - 2023

- Scholar from 8th grade to 4th year college
- · Does Public Speaking
- Part of Youth Organization
- Involves in many leadership training
- Part of Scholarship Officer. 2 years as a PRO and 1 year as a secretary
- · Organized some events and outreach programs like Golf Tournament and Cleaning of the Las Piñas - Parañaque Critical Habitat and Ecotourism Area (LPPCHEA) in southwest portion of Metro Manila and Manila Bay

#### 🜟 QCYDO Scholarship Program

#### 2019-2023

- Scholar from 1st year up to 4th year of college
- The Quezon City Youth Development Office (QCYDO) develops and implements services and programs that are sensitive to the needs and issues of the young people in the city



#### **TUNIFAST**

#### 2021-2023

• Scholar from 3rd year up to 4th year of college

# **REFERENCES**

### Prof. Norilyn C. Sindanum, MAIE

Assistant Professor I Quezon City University 09162219562

#### Clarissa M. Romero, LPT

Teacher I Holy Spirit National High School 09164398200

#### Kenneth C. Diolata

Support Specialist ISTA Personnel Solutions 09284740250